Cleanup Day
Closing
Ceremony
Address
Summer
Break
School
Cleanup Day
Closing
Ceremony
Address
Summer
Break
School
x becomes 4.
（教師）ｘは４となる。→
Substitute this value in the formula to calculate the value of y.
この値を公式に代入して
ｙの値が求められる。
Now you can derive the coordinates at the top, allowing you to draw a graph.
導き出せ
グラフが書けるというわけだ。
Gala Concert
（かをり）うらあー！
（公生）ギャー！
（公生）ううっ…。
（かをり）集中力　散漫！
You're totally distracted!
（公生）ちゃんと　やってるって！
I'm just doing what I'm supposed to!
Your playing was so timid!
嫌そうに弾いてた！
心ここにあらずな音！
Your heart wasn't in it at all!
ねえ
ガラコン　この曲じゃないと駄目？
Listen, does this have to be the
piece we play for the gala concert?
Oh, come on. What's wrong with it?
何よ　嫌なの？
もっと派手な方がいいよ
ガラコンは。
A concert like this calls for something with a little more flair.
Let's pick something more popular instead.
メジャーなやつにしよう。
やだぶー。　この曲がいいの。
No way!
This is the piece I wanna play!
Don't worry.
大丈夫　大丈夫。
私と君がやれば　派手になるって！
With the two of us playing it, it'll sound plenty flashy!
I wonder why you're being so shy about it.
君がそんなに嫌がるの　何でかな。
楽譜は　あんなに
愛にあふれていたのに…。
The score was overflowing with so much love for you.
《クライスラー　『愛の喜び』》
Kreisler's "Love's Joy."
"Love's Sorrow."
《『愛の悲しみ』》
"Love's Sorrow," the companion piece to Kreisler's "Love's Joy," was written for the violin.
＜クライスラー作　『愛の喜び』と対になる『愛の悲しみ』は　バイオリン曲＞
Rachmaninoff wrote a piano arrangement as well.
＜この曲には　ラフマニノフが編曲した
ピアノ版がある＞
あれ？　ここに差してたっけな。
Huh? Is this where I put it?
（早希）《また　ピアノの下で寝て》
Falling asleep under the piano again...
You're going to catch a cold.
（早希）《風邪ひくわよ》
《あっ…》
（早希）《重くなったわね。　公生》
You've grown, haven't you,
Kousei?
This is your punishment.
（早希）《これは　罰なのよ》→
《ピアノは
応えてくれないでしょ》
The piano won't answer you, will it?
《お前なんか
死んじゃえばいいんだ》
I wish you would just die.
《聞こえないよ。
助けて　お母さん》
I can't hear!
Help me, Mom!
《君が　そんなに嫌がるの
何でかな》
I wonder why you're being so shy about it.
どうしたって　母さんを
思い出しちゃうからだよ。
"Why"?
Because it reminds me of my mother.
（小春）きゃは。
Tiny Castellas
Hiroko, I've got to practice...
紘子さん　僕　練習が…。
（紘子）いいの　いいの。　気分転換。
息抜きも必要。
Forget about that!
A change of scenery will do you some good. You've gotta take some time to relax.
（小春）綿あめ　フラッペ。
（紘子）迷子になるなよ。
Cotton candy and frappes!
Hey, don't get lost out there!
ハァ…。
（紘子）
ラフマニノフ　『愛の悲しみ』→
Rachmaninoff's "Love's Sorrow."
Saki used to play that all the time, even when we were students.
早希は　学生のころから
よく弾いてたわ。
I heard it a lot as a lullaby.
子守歌代わりに
よく聴いてました。
この曲は　母さんのにおいが
し過ぎるんです。
This piece reminds me too much of my mother.
＜生々しく　色あでやかに
迫ってくる＞
It feels so raw and vivid as it closes in on me.
母さんは　僕を
憎んでたんじゃないでしょうか。
My mother must've really hated me, huh?
No mother in the world would hate her own child.
子供を憎む親なんか
いるもんですか。
That moment...
あのとき
あんたが人間として→
That was the moment you grew up, both as a person and as a pianist.
ピアニストとして成長した瞬間よ。早希が喜ばないはずがないわ。
There's no way it wouldn't have made Saki happy.
（母親）あっ　ここにいた。
ごめんね。
There you are!
I'm sorry!
（紘子）ちょっとだけ
さみしいけどね。
But it can be a bit lonely
子供が自分から離れていくのは…。
watching your child grow apart from you.
母さんは
僕を許してくれるでしょうか。
Do you think...
Do you think my mother will forgive me?
I've tried so hard to forget all about her.
必死で
母さんを忘れようとした僕を。
Is it okay for me to play the piano?
僕は　ピアノを弾いて
いいんでしょうか？
（紘子）だったら弾こうよ。→
If that's how you feel, then play.
迷いがあるなら
びしっと　ピアノ弾いて→
Play with conviction in the face of whatever's holding you back.
早希の声を聞こうよ。
Try to hear Saki's voice.
声…。
Her voice...
"Don't fret over such ridiculous things.
（紘子）バカなことで
悩んでないで→
さっさと
一人前になりなさいって。
Become a man who can stand up for himself."
弾こう。
私たちは　ピアニストだよ。
Let's play.
We're both pianists, after all.
Candy apple!
りんごあめ。
りんごあめ　嫌い？
You don't like candy apples?
ああっ　違うんだ！
食べたことなくて…。
No, that's not it! I've just never had one before...
（小春の泣き声）
わ～！　泣かないで！
Don't cry!
（小春の泣き声）
食べる　食べるから。　ありがとう。
I'll eat it! See?
Thanks.
（紘子）
《酷なこと言ってるかしら》→
Maybe I'm being too harsh with him.
《でも弾かなきゃ》→
It looks tasty.
But he has to play.
So that he can mature as a pianist.
《ピアニストとして
成長するために》
うん　おいしい。
It's good!
（紘子）《お別れするために》
So that he can say goodbye.
んもー！
遅くなっちゃったじゃない。
Jeez, look how late it is!
Gala Concert
君が粘るからでしょ！　わがまま。
That's because you were too stubborn to give up!
君だって
いちゃもん　つけてたじゃん！
What about you?! You wouldn't
stop whining about the selection!
う～ん！
本当に遅くなっちゃって→
I wonder if your folks are gonna be mad at us for coming home so late.
家の人　怒ってないかなあ。
あっ　ねえ　見て　見て！　空！
Hey, look up at the sky!
Are you ignoring me?!
無視！？
星が奇麗だよ。
The stars are so beautiful.
星が話し掛けてるみたい。
It's like they're speaking to us!
（公生・かをり）♪♪「Ｕｐ　ａｂｏｖｅ
ｔｈｅ　ｗｏｒｌｄ　ｓｏ　ｈｉｇｈ」→
ケーキ屋さん。
ただいまー。
A bakery?
I'm home!
ちょっと　待ってて。
僕　もう帰るよ。
Wait here for a sec.
I'm just gonna head home.
What the hell do you want with my daughter?!
（かをりの父）
うちの娘に何の用だ！
あの　僕…。
（かをりの父）うー！
Uh...
I...
（かをりの父）あっ。　有馬君？
えっ？
Arima?
（かをりの母）有馬君？
Well, if it ain't Arima!
有馬君じゃないかー！
（かをりの母）きゃー！
It's just leftover stock, but have your fill, okay?
（かをりの母）残り物だけど
じゃんじゃん食べてね。
あっ…　ありがとうございます。
Th-Thank you very much!
試作品もあったな。
もう　じゅうぶん頂いてますから。
We've got some samples, too, right?
Please, I've already had more than enough!
うちの両親は　君のファンなの。
My parents are fans of yours.
They went to your competitions all the time when we were kids.
小さいころ　コンクールに
よく来てたよ。
I heard the whole story, Arima!
（かをりの父）聞いたよ　有馬君！
ひっ！
You shouldn't abort your performances.
演奏を中止したら　いかんよ。
今までの苦労が　全部パーだ。
That's like flushing all your struggles down the drain!
うん　うん。　スポンジが
しっとり仕上がっても→
It's like baking a moist sponge cake, only for it to be totally ruined by some god-awful cream!
クリームが　くそまずくて
台無しみたいなもんよ。
うん　うん。
すみません。
Sorry about that.
でも　その破天荒な若さ
いいね！　やるじゃん！
Still, I like a young man who breaks the mold!
Good for you!
胃袋に入っちまえば一緒よね。
材料　同じなんだし。
There's no difference once it's in your stomach, since the ingredients are all the same.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
（かをりの父）
小学校のかをりの写真　見るかい？
Want to see some pictures of Kaori from grade school?
（かをりの父）カワイイぞ！
（かをりの母）幼稚園のもあるわよ。
She was so adorable!
We have some from kindergarten, too!
駄目ー！
Don't you dare!
（かをりの父）これ　うちの人に。
Here, for your folks.
ありがとうございます。
今日は　ごちそうさまでした。
I appreciate it.
And thank you for all the cake.
ガラコンサートは
応援に行くからね。
We'll be cheering you on at the gala concert.
頑張ってね！
はい。　頑張ります。
Good luck!
Thanks. I'll do my best.
通りまで　送ってくる。
I'll walk you to the main street.
あの子が　有馬君か。
So that's Arima, huh?
礼儀正しい　いい子じゃないか。
（かをりの母）ええ。
Seems like a good, well-mannered kid, don't you think?
Yeah.
もー！　生まれたころの写真まで
持ち出して！
Like, really?! They even hauled out the baby pictures!
しかも全裸！　お嫁にいけない！
Buck naked and all!
Now I can never get married!
明るい　ご両親だね。
You sure have cheerful parents.
My mom's always stuffing starving dogs with food.
ママったら　ひもじい犬に
やたら餌をあげるのよね。
"Starving"?
《ひもじい…》
あれ？
Huh?
君　身長　伸びた？
Did you get taller?
えっ？　あっ　どうかな？
I'm not sure.
そっか。　もう顔が
下　向いてないからだね。
Oh, I get it.
It's because you're not looking down anymore.
それにしても　ことしは暑いね。
Anyway, it sure is hot this year.
＜たわいもない会話。
よくある風景＞
A meaningless conversation.
Familiar scenery.
It's so humid!
じめじめするよー。　鳴りが悪い。
I can't stand it.
もわっとするよね。
Don't you think it's muggy?
＜それでも　よく覚えているのは
たぶん…＞
Even so, the reason I remember it so well is probably...
でもさ
夏は花火があるから好きだな。
Oh, but I do like summer for the fireworks.
＜きっと…＞
♪♪（『キラキラ星』の鼻歌）
I'm sure...
Your Lie in April
＜夏の夜のせいだ＞
it's all because of that summer night.
Your Lie in April
Gala Concert
I told you!
だからー！
そこ　もっと優雅に歌わせてよ！
Make that part flow more elegantly!
The accompanist can't just ignore what's written!
伴奏は　指示　無視しちゃ駄目だろ。バイオリンが目立たなくなるよ！
Otherwise, the violin won't stand out!
Will, too! 'Cause I'm the one playing it!
目立つよ　私が弾くんだもん！
（渡）平和だ。
All's right with the world.
You're so arrogant!
傲岸不遜！
私に合わせてよ！
Just follow my lead!
Where's my green tea and red bean shaved ice?
It's not that simple! You runaway horse!
（椿）私の宇治金時は？
（渡）んっ？→
Huh? I'm eating it.
俺　食ってるけど。
（椿）人でなし！→
You monster!
That was my shaved ice!
私の宇治金時…。　もうやだ。
補習　出たくない。→
I can't go on!
I don't want to go to summer school!
遊びたい。　お祭り　行きたい。
（柏木）平和だ。
I want to play!
I want to go to the festival!
All's right with the world.
I want to light some fireworks!
（椿）花火　したい！
おっ！
採用！
（柏木）うん？
Done!
（椿）アハハハ！　初花火！
奇麗～。
The first fireworks of the year!
So pretty!
バレないかな？
プールに忍び込んで花火なんか…。
Are you sure we're not gonna get caught sneaking in here to light firecrackers?
平気　平気。
（渡）先生は　みんな帰ったしな。
Oh, no worries!
All the teachers have gone home anyway.
（椿）水なら
いっぱい確保してあるしね。
And we've got plenty of water at our disposal.
Lay off the rockets, got it?
（渡）でもロケット花火はやめとけ。（椿・かをり）うっ！
（柏木）プッ…。
《柏木さん…》
Kashiwagi...
あ～　また　あした補習か。
More summer school tomorrow...
まあ　諦めろ。
Well, just suck it up.
頭の悪い　お前が悪い。
（椿）むっ。→
It's your fault for being a moron.
うるせー！　推薦組が！
Shut up, you lousy scholarship student!
あんたたちは　どうすんの？
（公生・かをり）うん？
What are you two gonna do?
I mean for high school.
進路よ。　補習も出てないし。
やっぱ　２人とも音大系に進むの？
Since you're not attending summer school,
does that mean you're on the music-college track?
私は…。
I'm...
先のことは考えてないや。
I haven't thought about the future.
For now, I'm gonna rock the audience at the gala and steal the spotlight!
取りあえず　今は
ガラコンで　観客　沸かせて→
主役の座は　頂くわ。
私たち　最強だもん！
We're the almighty duo, after all!
（渡）その意気　その意気！
ヘヘヘ。
Yeah, that's the spirit!
ほい～！
おお～　派手～！
Awesome!
（渡）フウー　フウー　フウー！
フウー！
（渡）ハハハハ！　フフフウー！
（かをり・渡の笑い声）
《うん。　絵になる２人だ》
Yeah.
Those two look great together.
危ないってば。
（椿）あっ。
That's dangerous!
I could say the same!
What are you gaping at?!
（椿）何を見とんじゃ！
何で！？　ああっ！
Why?!
（柏木）ハァ…。
（椿・かをり）わあー！
It's pitch black at the bottom.
＜真っ暗の底　音も聞こえない＞
I can't hear a sound.
It's like my...
＜まるで　僕の…＞
《助けて　助けてよ》
Help me.
Please help me!
《何も聞こえないよ。
暗い　暗い…》
I can't hear anything.
Enveloped in darkness.
（紘子）
《音が聞こえないってことは→
Not hearing the notes you play could mean you're not bound by auditory perception.
聴覚的な音に束縛されない
ってことじゃないかな》
《音に束縛されない？》
I'm not bound by sound?
（紘子）
《自分の中にあるイメージ》→
You've been letting the imagery within you
《自分の奥底から
湧き上がる音を→
and the sounds that rise up from the bottom of your
soul override everything else without realizing it.
知らず知らずのうちに
優先させているのよ》
《自分の中の音。　心象風景》→
Wasn't there ever a moment when you sensed all those thoughts and all that imagery
permeating the notes with your desires and emotions?
《願いや思いを込めた音を
感じる瞬間はなかった？》→
《音が聞こえなくなる》→
Losing your ability to hear yourself play is nothing short of a gift.
《きっと　それは贈り物だよ》
A gift?
《贈り物…》
Close your eyes, cover your ears, and just play as you feel.
《目を閉じて　耳をふさいで
今は心のままに弾きなさい》
《あんたには
じゅうぶん技術がある》→
You have the technical ability to pull that off.
The ability to trace the sounds that you see within yourself.
《自分の中にある音
イメージする音をトレースできる技術》
It's a memento that Saki left behind for you.
《それは
早希があんたに残した思い出》
Did you get taller?
《身長　伸びた？》
Oh, I get it.
《そっか。　もう顔が
下　向いてないからだね》
It's because you're not looking down anymore.
《顔を上げてるからだね》
It's because you're looking up now!
《♪♪「ターン　ターン
タタン　タターン」》
（椿・渡）公生！
Kousei!
Are you okay?!
（渡）公生！
あっ。
（渡・公生）あっ…！
生きてる！
He's alive!
痛がってる。
（椿）生きてる証拠だ。
He's in pain!
That's proof that he's alive!
何で？
How could you?
何で　足　着くプールで
溺れてんのよ。
How could you drown in such a shallow pool?!
私のせいになるじゃんよ。
Everyone's gonna blame me!
He freakin' slammed his head right into his savior's face!
命の恩人に頭突きくれやがった。
（柏木）やるな。
Well played.
Is it the pool?
＜プールだから？＞
＜月が出てるからかな？＞
Or because the moon's out?
＜もしかしたら　暗い海の底にも
光は差すのかもしれない＞
Maybe—
just maybe—
light can reach even the bottom of a dark sea.
Gala Concert
Miyazono's playing too, right?
（観客）宮園さんも出るんでしょ。
Yeah. She's the girl who stopped playing in the middle of her performance.
（観客）ああ　あの演奏中断した子。
主催者も思い切るわ。
The people who run this thing must be crazy.
（観客）逆にインパクトありよ。
楽しみ。
But that actually made an impact. I'm so excited!
（観客）今日はちゃんと弾くかしら。
I wonder if she'll play it right today.
She'll probably go wild with it again.
（観客）また暴れるんじゃないの？
（観客）彼女目当てで来たんだもの。
Well, I came today just to see her.
（三池）ふんっ。
（絵見）《よし！
誰も知り合いがいない！》
All right! There's nobody I know around here.
（落合）絵見？
（絵見）ぎゃほ！　あー…。
Emi?
座らないの？
（絵見）落合先生！→
Aren't you going to take your seat?
Ms. Ochiai?!
Um... who's this "Emi"?
アハハ　絵見って？
有馬君の伴奏の件
教えたのは私よ。
I'm the one who told you about
Arima being an accompanist today.
I-It's not like I came here to see Arima!
（絵見）べべべ…　別に
私は　有馬とは関係なく→
純粋に　バババ…　バイオリンを…。（落合）はい　あなたのプログラム。
I-I'm just here to enjoy some v-violin music...
Here's your program.
ああっ…。
（落合）行きましょう。
Let's go.
It'll be starting soon.
ぼちぼち始まるわよ。
You witch!
（絵見）《魔女め！》
（風間）《ガラコンは審査がない分
純粋に楽しめる》
There's no judging at gala concerts, so we can just sit back and enjoy ourselves.
With the level of talent here, we can enjoy each performance just as much as anyone else.
（審査員）《さすがに
このレベルになると→
普通に聴ける。
さて　俺の本命は　そろそろかな》
Now, then. Is it almost time for my favorite?
Miyazono Kaori
Sumiya Junior High
Pianist: Arima Kousei
F. Kreisler  Love's Sorrow
Past Accolades: N/A
何やっとんじゃー！
What does she think she's doing?!
バイオリニストが来ないなんて非常識！
（小春）わ～　ハハハ…！
The violinist a no-show?! That's just insane!
ミケランジェリかよ！
ポゴレリッチかよ！
Who is she, Michelangeli?! Pogorelich?!
The show's started.
（椿）始まっちゃったよ。
まだ　かをちゃん　来てないの？
Is Kao not here yet?
どうすんじゃー！
（紘子）宮園かをりって→
Is Miyazono Kaori this unpredictable?
ここまで破天荒なの？
さっきから　携帯
鳴らしてんだけど　全然　出ねえよ。
I've been calling her cell phone, but she won't pick up.
Watari
This is serious. I can't...
困ったな。　これじゃ…。
Let's go in and get prepared.
私たちは　中に入って準備しよう。
いつ　宮園が来てもいいように。
We'll be ready for her whenever she shows up.
お願い。
宮園の携帯　鳴らしてて。
Please keep calling Miyazono's phone.
Yes, ma'am!
はい！　お姉さま！
（紘子）お願いね。
I'm counting on you.
（渡）はっ！
（椿）頑張って！
Ma'am!
Good luck!
どうします？
What should we do?
順番ずらしてもらえるか
頼んでみる。
I'll go ask if they'll move you guys down the list.
It's only a gala concert, so they might be a little more flexible.
ガラコンだから
ある程度は融通が利くかも。
演奏者の了解さえ　取れれば
ぎりぎりまで　宮園を待てる。
As long as we can get the performers to agree,
we can wait on Miyazono till the last possible second.
＜何で＞
Why...
If that doesn't pan out, we'll just have to forget it.
（紘子）それが無理なら
諦めるしかないわ。
そうですね。
Yeah, I guess so.
＜何でだよ＞
But why?
《君はどうする？》
What will you do?
《この曲がいい！》
This is the piece I wanna play!
Weren't you looking forward to this?
＜君は
楽しみにしてたんじゃないの？＞
＜浮かれてた僕が　バカみたいだ＞
I was an idiot for getting carried away.
もうすぐ　宮園かをりだな。
It's almost Miyazono Kaori's turn.
I wonder what's in store this time!
今度は　何やってくるかな。
（審査員）《こんなに
わくわくするの　久しぶりだな》
It's been a while since I've felt this excited.
（実行委員）困ります。
（紘子）お願い！→
That's unacceptable!
Please! She's on a bus heading here right now!
今　バスで　こっちに向かってるの。
（実行委員）そうは言いましても
私の一存では…。
Be that as it may, I don't have the authority to...
（三池）どうしたんですか？
What's going on?
（実行委員）三池君。
（紘子）三池君って…。
Miike?
Miike? He's the final act of the junior high division?
確か　中学生の部のトリの…。
Yes, since he won the competition.
（実行委員）ええ　彼は
コンクールの優勝者ですから。
ナイスタイミング！
（三池）あっ。
Nice timing!
Sorry, but could you let them play after you?
悪いけど
順番を後にしてもらえないかな？
うちのバイオリニストが
遅れてるの。
Our violinist's running late.
遅れてる？
（紘子）宮園かをりって子なの。→
Running late?
Her name's Miyazono Kaori.
すぐ来ると思うの。
君の後にしてもらえないかな？
I'm sure she'll be here soon.
Do you think you could let her play after you?
（観客）
《宮園さんも出るんでしょ？》
Miyazono's playing too, right?
I'm so excited!
（観客）《楽しみ》
嫌です。
Absolutely not.
このガラコンのトリは
主役は僕です。
The starring role of this concert's final act...
belongs to me.
まあ　だよねえ。
Well, of course it does.
《晴れの舞台だもんな。
悪いのは僕らだ》
It's your moment of triumph, after all.
We only have ourselves to blame.
I apologize for being so presumptuous.
ごめんなさいね
無茶なこと言って。
出演　キャンセルしかなさそうね。
Looks like we're going to have to withdraw.
ええ。
だ…　だいたい→
Yeah.
A-Anyway, it's her own fault for being late on a day like this.
遅れてくる方が悪いんだ。
こんな日に。
演奏が　めちゃくちゃだから
生活態度だって　めちゃくちゃなんだ。
Her playing's such a mess—it's no
wonder her lifestyle's so chaotic, too.
（三池）ちょっと　ウケたからって
特別だと思って→
She thinks she's special just because an audience
kind of liked her, so she shows up late like it's nothing.
平気で遅刻してくる。
何も　そこまで…。
（三池）現に　そうじゃないですか！
You don't have to go that far...
But am I wrong?!
音楽は　譜面の中にあるんだ。→
The music is written in the score.
What she produces is disastrous.
あんなの　めちゃくちゃ。
音楽でも　何でもない。
It's not even music!
小僧が　何　生意気なこと
言ってんのよ！
Who do you think you are, you little brat?!
分かりました。
演奏前に　お騒がせして→
All right, then.
Sorry for disturbing you before your performance.
すみませんでした。
ちょっと　公生！
Hey, Kousei!
悔しくないわけ？
パートナー　けなされてんのよ！？
Aren't you pissed at all?
He insulted your partner!
プログラムどおり→
Let's go by the program.
中学生の部のトリは
三池さんで　お願いします。
The final act of the junior high division is yours, Miike.
ただ…。
However...
The spotlight!
《主役の座は…》
今日の主役の座は
僕らが　もらいます。
Today's spotlight belongs to us.
[ﾏｲｸ]（アナウンス）中学の部
主催者推薦　宮園かをりさん。
The promoters' choice for the junior high division, Ms. Miyazono Kaori.
（観客）来た。
（観客）いよいよだ。
Here she comes!
At last.
It's Miyazono.
（椿）《間に合ったの？》
（観客）宮園かをりだ。
She got here in time?
It's Miyazono Kaori!
（観客）あれ？
Huh?
Isn't he the accompanist?
（観客）彼は　伴奏者でしょ。
Where's the violinist?
（観客）バイオリニストは？
宮園さんは？
Where's Miyazono?
（絵見）《有馬？　まさか１人で》
（風間）《前代未聞》
Arima, surely you're not playing alone?
Unprecedented!
（椿）公生…。
Kousei...
Episode 12
Twinkle, Little Star
Episode 13
Love's Sadness
sore zore no yume wo erande
No two dreams can be the same
Episode 13
Love's Sadness
sore zore no yume wo erande
No two dreams can be the same
（今田）あしたの夜７時からは…。
（４人）『ザ・ドキドキどっきり』
今日は　あしたの放送に
先駆けまして→
前回放送の　爆笑どっきりを
ご覧ください。
（東野）たくさんございましたよね。（３人）はい。
何でやねん。　おかしいな。
僕も軽く聞いてるんで。
いいです　いいです。